[Music]
Listen,
what's up?  If you forgot to call me for chole, do
n't tell me, I am feeling sleepy.   The
chickpeas are not to be puffed.
So don't even ask me to turn off the lights.
You came later, you should have closed it.
Hey brother, listen first.
You are the one who tells me stories during the day and I
listen to you at night too.  We wo
n't be able to hear you [nasal sound] anymore.  Lie down
quietly.
Why are you wasting your time
?  We were saying that we should go a
week before Rakshabandhan.
For a week.
Now we go only once a year, so let it be for
a week.
Tell me how much you love us.  Ca
n't live without me even for a week.  Looks like he got
angry and left.  Leave aside a week, I will wait for just
two days for the poor guy.
Hey, take out this big briefcase.  She will
come after waiting for at least a month.  [Music] If it's
not there, then put some in this too, Papa.
Yes, this is also fine.
What is this happening?   I have
taken out both the briefcase and the bag for you.   At
this late hour?
Yes, leave by the first train in the morning.
Papa has even booked the ticket and the
return ticket is for a month later.
Tell me, I was wondering how much these people
care about us.  These people cannot live without us.
What a cruelty this is, God.
Mom, don't worry about us.  Poor Roh
became overwhelmed with joy.  Yes.